Dylan Casanova

Dyylancasanova17@gmail.com| (210)-577-9853 | Austin, Texas 78717

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dylan-casanova-7b8b37211/ | Github: https://github.com/Dylan-Casanova
Portfolio: https://github.com/Dylan-Casanova

Full stack web developer who graduated from The University of Texas at Austin. Passionate about learning and approaching programming challenges from different angles and collaborating with others to create meaningful and proficient web applications. With over 5 years of experience working for financial institutions, I am interested in connecting financial experience with web development or taking on new challenges.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, RESTful APIs, MySQL, NodeJS, NoSQL, MongoDB, React, and Github.

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Travel-Mentor

Co-developer | Deployed application | Github repo

- A website that searches for travel tips in the form of videos, books and guides
- Built with JavaScript, HTML and CSS

Employee-Tracker

Developer | Github repo | Video demo |

- Command line application for employee tracking
- Built with MySQL and JavaScript

ECommerce-Back End

Developer | Github repo | Video demo

- An application that allows a client/user to update, view and add information/data to a database.
- Built with Insomnia and MySQL and JavaScript

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Financial Crime Specialist

September 2019 – February 2021

Wells Fargo, San Antonio, TX

Job Duties/accomplishments

- Effectively investigate transactions flagged as fraudulent by utilizing available resources and reaching out to managers or colleagues when needed.
- Successfully managed 40-50 inbound customer calls per day, consistently ranking among the top three out of 20+ agents on my team.
- Diligently researched customer's banking activity to make a final decision whether claim should be paid or denied.

Teller Part time

February 2018 – September 2019

Wells Fargo, San Antonio, TX

Job Duties/accomplishments

- Successfully managed cash drawer containing between \$10,000 \$50,000 at any given time by providing undivided attention to customer's request.
- Purposefully provide excellent customer service by engaging in meaningful dialogue to identify potential banking needs.
- Effectively helped resolve customer banking concerns and vigorously followed policy and procedures put in place to minimize errors and reduce fraud.
- Collaborated with team members who take pride in performing well and enjoy helping others to create a healthy, safe and enjoyable work environment

Personal Banker

August 2017 – February 2018

Wells Fargo, San Antonio, TX

Job Duties/accomplishments

- Enthusiastically built relationships with customers by getting to know the customer's financial situation and goals.
- Effectively asked meaningful questions to understand what is important to the customer and be able to recommend or suggest products/services that will benefit the customer.
- Helped between 15-20 customers in a diligent manner to ensure they have the financial knowledge necessary to manage their monetary assets effectively on a daily basis.

Lead Teller

February 2017 – July 2017

Wells Fargo, San Antonio, TX

Job Duties/accomplishments

- Energetically led team of 5 or more tellers, managing schedules, performance reviews and daily tasks.
- Effectively helped other team members to deal with difficult customers by analyzing the problem and suggesting potential solutions
- Actively assisted with workflow to ensure tellers are successful and customers satisfied. By being flexible with schedule and helping other teller's lines when my line was empty.
- Consistently balance teller's cash, counting between \$10,000 \$50,000.
- Meticulously balance main bank vaults, cash counting between \$100,000 \$500,000 on a daily basis.

Teller

August 2015 – January 2017

Wells Fargo, San Antonio, TX

Job Duties/accomplishments

My job duties and accomplishments as a teller are very similar to those referred to in the **Teller** part time and **Lead Teller** section. To avoid redundancy, I have decided to write this explanation instead.

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Austin
Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

2021

Texas A&M University-San Antonio Bachelor's degree of Science in Psychology

2018 – Present